Enemies?
What nation's battleship is that?
It probably belongs to
the Bloodchain Brigade.
What? The Bloodchain Brigade?
So the rats scurried right into the trap?
Rats?
The Bloodchain Brigade are the most
extreme of the anti-Highlander factions.
They've been getting out of hand,
and it's become a problem.
So I set a trap.
You knew about the Bloodchain Brigade?
Obviously.
A trap, you say?
Nothing complicated.
We just set up a fake ceremony.
Then I, an Arch Lord, attended.
A fake ceremony?
Then the new Hyral Menas...?
That was a lie, of course.
Our goal was to lure the rats out
into the open and exterminate them.
So we were just pawns, then?
Then why did His Majesty
have to face such humiliation?
None of you have meaning!
None of you have value!
You're all worthless, helpless trash that
can't do anything but crawl on the ground!
That's so cruel!
Wonderful!
So what you're saying
is that you're a bad guy
who not only lied to our king,
but also cut off his arm.
I've got that right, don't I?
Yup. I commend you for your excellent
understanding of the situation.
Your Majesty, order me to strike
this criminal down, and I will.
You must not kill him.
Capture him alive.
As you wish.
You heard the man.
So the situation has changed.
I'll be taking you up on that duel.
Sure, but I've got other
people to fight today.
Let's make it quick.
Give me all you've got!
Thank you!
Is that pale light... magic?
No, it's nothing I've ever sensed before.
This woman's a threat
like none I've ever seen...
So I'll...
Come on. The second you touch this wall,
you'll lose an arm or a leg,
just like that knight and your king did!
What's wrong?
Come and get me.
That magic, it's an "annihilation" effect
that destroys whatever touches it, right?
How did she know?
Can she see this wall?
It looks like surrounding your whole body
with it weakened the effects.
It'd be stronger if you concentrated
your power in one spot.
Go ahead and do that, please.
I'll attack that point.
Are you stupid?
If I do that, and you just attack
a different spot, I'm finished!
If I wanted to do that,
I'd already have attacked you.
You can't believe me?
For a Highlander Arch Lord,
you're kind of a coward.
Nice!
Chris!
Come on! I'll just pray you're not a liar!
Of course! Here I go!
If I use an aether-imbued attack
to destroy the magic structure itself...
Oops!
Where do you think he fell?
Well, that's Chris for you...
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 11      Butt-Kicking Squire
We have no choice now but to
destroy the Bloodchain Brigade!
We may be able to use that to restore
relations with the Highland.
Go!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Sire, please evacuate.
Everyone but His Majesty's guards,
go on the attack!
Yes, sir!
We'll go engage the Bloodchain Brigade, then.
"We"?
Chris, I'm a little tired after
healing His Majesty's arm...
If you want to rest, you can rest near me.
Wherever you are is bound to be
where the fighting's fiercest!
It's fine! Come on, come on!
Fine! Fine! Well...
I'll be back later!
She seems like someone I can count on.
Over there!
A Flying Gear!
No time for that!
Sorry to bother you!
Wh-What the heck?!
What is that?
A maid! It's an airborne maid!
She's fast!
There we go.
Look, Rani. We're almost at the
Bloodchain Brigade's battleship.
I knew it'd be the front line...
We need to stop them now,
before they hurt more innocents.
Here we go, Chris!
Oh, you're all ready to fight now, huh, Rani?
After seeing that, yeah.
I'll interrupt their attack.
What are you going to do?
Go!
Burst!
Circle the ship!
I see. You're blinding them.
I'll stop their attacks. You stop the ship!
Okay, got it!
Aether Strike!
They deflected it?!
I knew it...
Leon and Sistia don't seem to be there.
That little girl did that?
How can a maid be that powerful?
Welcome.
I'll be serving you this evening.
That was just my way of welcoming you.
S-Serving us?
Be careful.
The more beautiful the rose, the sharper
its thorns and deadlier its poison.
Continue the mission. I'll deal with her.
What about your plan
to save the Hyral Menas?
The principal and my friends
from the academy are handling it.
And if we don't do anything,
they might think we're with you.
So the two of us came to protect
the king and the Highlander emissary.
Doesn't splitting your forces make it
more likely that you'll fail on both fronts?
If I take care of things here
and get over there before they finish,
I get to have twice the fun!
How bold.
While you're being bold, why don't you
tell me where the Highlander emissary is?
Oh, sorry...
I actually don't know.
That's a shame.
It appears you've grown stronger than before.
I didn't have a way
of determining that for myself.
But you seem like the perfect opportunity!
So you're using me as a way
to test yourself?
Thanks in advance!
I guess I have no choice, then.
It seems something did happen at the castle!
All the troops that were escorting Ripple
headed back to the castle.
Now is our chance.
Okay.
Everyone, I'll say this again: you're under no
obligation to participate in this operation.
Please don't feel like you have to.
Who's going to go home
after being told that?
Nobody here is going home.
Actually, in that case,
I'm gonna go home and sleep.
Wait! Wait, Yua!
We need you here!
You just said I didn't have to do it.
We need your help.
Please lend us your aid.
Mr. Glasses, do you have a fever?
No!
I'm just fine!
Oh, you're right. You get mad so fast.
Depending on who I'm talking to!
This isn't the time!
We're about to start the mission!
I'm asking you to stay, too.
I could really use you on my side.
Ripple...
I thought I had no choice but to accept
what was happening to me.
A Hyral Menas who can't protect anyone...
is no Hyral Menas at all.
But you're all doing your absolute best
to protect me, right?
Well, one of you seems
to just be having fun.
True. I won't say who, though.
She's probably sneezing right now.
I'm sure she is.
The home where I was born
was destroyed years and years ago.
But now this country is my home.
I can really feel that now.
I understand how I really feel...
I know I'm causing trouble for you all,
but I want to stay here with
the people of this country.
So... it's only natural that
I'd ask for help, right?
Ripple...
So, Yua...
Yua, Ripple is begging for your help—
Zzz...
Hey!
He's interrupting my sleep!
Save me, Lady Animal Ears!
Anyway, I want your help.
If it works out, I'll buy you dinner, okay?
I don't want food. I want you to
introduce me to somebody.
What kind of person?
Somebody as cool as Mr. Glasses.
Wh-What? It's too late for you to try
and get on my good side—
Somebody who's not as short-tempered
or weak as Mr. Glasses...
Why, you...
Okay, now that we've made it to the
punchline, I'd like to start the mission!
The punchline? Ma'am...
Go ahead, Leone.
Okay!
Principal Miliera and I will have Ripple
absorb our power and summon magicite beasts.
You take them out when they show up!
It's in your hands, everyone.
Spread out in a circle around Ripple!
Here they come!
Such incredible power!
I can see why you're the leader
of the Bloodchain Brigade!
Chris, I believe in you!
Sorry. I'm not done yet.
That's more than fine by me!
I can sense one more aether flow,
besides his Aether Shell.
An aether sword?
I'm amazed you dodged that. Impressive.
That sword's made of compressed
and stabilized aether, isn't it?
I can use magic to create a sword too, but...
Wielding a compressed aether sword and
aether armor simultaneously is no mean feat.
I can't do that myself yet.
It is as you say.
Sorry, but you're mine!
At this distance, he has the advantage.
I need to get closer!
But that sword...
If I take a hit from that, even with my
Aether Shell, I won't be getting off lightly.
Which means...
I've got one chance!
That weak blade can't stop me!
It doesn't need to!
If it can halt him for even
a second, I can get close!
Aether Strike!
She's approaching the point
where even I can't stop her?
It sounds like you've been busy.
But I've been focusing on training.
Chris, something's coming! Focus!
Ivel! I'm so glad you're okay!
What? You were the one who
kicked me into the sky!
Arch Lord... You're the emissary this time?
So you're the leader
of the Bloodchain Brigade?
What a stupid-looking costume.
Get back, Ivel. He's after your life.
That's exactly what I want!
I'm going to crush their leader,
before moving on to the rest of the maggots!
Then I suppose I'll need to defend myself.
Wait! That's no reason to fight each other!
Why can't we all just get along?
You're one to talk!
Of course, if you'd both like to fight me...
I've secured the bridge.
Well done, Sistia.
Things have become rather complicated.
Sistia, lend me your strength.
With pleasure.
My power, my being... Use them as you like.
I entrust it all to you.
The Hyral Menas is becoming a weapon?
Not if I can help it!
Amazing!
It's absorbing aether,
rather than mana, and amplifying it!
The Hyral Menas lives up to their reputation!
Gotcha.
You really are amazing, Yua.
Thank you, Curly Hair.
But I'm a little tired...
I think we're at our limits.
Leone...
Thank you!
Nice, Two.
She's using her spatial isolation Gift
at the same time... Well done.
Thank you.
But... sorry. I think I'm at my limit...
Is this all we can do?
Let's defeat the magicite beasts
in front of us, at least!
No!
Lightning beasts? Is that...
Brother?
Hey.
So, um... I'm sure you have a lot
you want to say to me.
But I'm going to help you.
Hey, don't look so mad.
You saw that, right? I'm here to help.
Do you know how much Leone has suffered?
Do you think you can atone
by helping us here?
I understand.
Here.
What is that?
Mana mist.
It should help you.
He's right... My body feels so light...
That's a big help!
Yeah, my new boss has a lot
of helpful stuff.
He's the one who told me
to come here, actually.
You shouldn't keep your desire for justice
bottled up within you.
If there's something you want
to protect, go protect it.
So I didn't have a choice. No choice at all.
"No choice"?
Leone, seal us all in pocket space again.
You're still doubting me?
I'm not going to try and trick you.
I-I know!
You're actually a little glad
I'm here, aren't you?
I am not!
You're feeding mana to Ripple, right?
Silva...
Right.
Get ready, everybody.
Chris! Look!
It's from the direction of the academy.
Hey, you okay?
Brother, what was that?
Look.
Ripple summoned something unbelievable.
That's... a Prismer!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Don't you wish
we could've
worn cute
outfits too?
Comic by Kuromura Moto